# **Abhishek Suresh Savkar**

Web Developer at Syscomss Solutions

2 Year(s) 0 Month(s) | Nasik | INR 2.40 Lac(s)

9158497252 abhisheksavkar02@gmail.com

"MCS with 2 years of experience in Web Developer

#### **WORK SUMMARY**

Web Developer at Syscomss SolutionsKey knowledge areas in Web Development: ? Good understanding of HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, AngularJS, CSS Frameworks, Responsive Design, Browser Developer Tools, Building & Automation Tools / Web Performance. Advanced programming and design skills. Landing page development. SEO. Project Management. Strong collaborative skills. Website Optimization. Excellent problem solving skills. Completed Website:

http://www.elegancedecorstudio.com/ http://www.indiansafaries.com/

https://www.tessrnet.com/ http://www.imaainstitution.org/

http://www.blossomkitchenindia.com/ http://www.ashartacademy.com/

http://www.krishnawriting.com/ http://www.devrajgroups.com/

http://www.dileepmehendale.com/ http://www.ibcinstitute.in/

http://www.linewidthinteriors.com/ http://www.nashikinfrastructure.com/

http://www.rampawarphotography.com/ http://www.roopdarshanphotostudio.co.in/

http://www.sanmaniso.com/

**Industry**: IT-Software/Software Services

Functional Area: Design / Creative / User Experience

Role: Web Designer

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Nasik Aug 2016 - Aug 2016

**Syscomss Solutions** 

Web Developer

Web Developer Jul 2016 - Till Date

# **Syscomss Solutions**

Advanced Web Developer with 2 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing interactive website. Innovative use of technology and SEO to drive traffic and engage users.

#### **FDUCATION DETAILS**

P.G.

MS/M.Sc(Science) (Computers) 2015

Pune University

U.G.

B.Sc (Computers) 2013

Pune University

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Creative Web Design

# **IT SKILLS**

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Dreamweaver, Photoshop			

#### **DESIRED JOB DETAILS**

Job Type: Permanent

**Employment Status :** Full time **US Work Status :** Not Mentioned

**Preferred Location:** Nasik

# **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Name: Abhishek Suresh Savkar

**Gender**: Male

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Date of Birth: 02 Feb 1992

Address: A/P Jopul. Tal- Dindori, Dist- Nashik. Jopul.-422209

Mobile: 9158497252(M)

Email ID: abhisheksavkar02@gmail.com

#### **CANDIDATE TEXT RESUME**

Abhishek Suresh Savkar

Email: abhisheksavkar02@gmail.com

Mobile: +91-9158497252

PROFILE SUMMARY

• Advanced web developer with 2+ years of experience in structuring, developing and

implementing interactive websites. Innovative use of technology and SEO to drive traffic and engage users. Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with attractive, user-friendly websites.

#### ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

■ Name of Company: Syscomss Solutions. (www.syscomss.com)

Designation: Web Developer. Duration: 1st July 2016 to till date.

Key knowledge areas in Web Development:

- Good understanding of HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, AngularJS, CSS Frameworks, Responsive Design, Browser Developer Tools, Building & Automation Tools / Web Performance.
- Advanced programming and design skills.
- Landing page development.
- SEO.
- Project Management.
- Strong collaborative skills.
- Website Optimization.
- Excellent problem solving skills.

# Completed Website:

- http://www.elegancedecorstudio.com/
- http://www.indiansafaries.com/
- https://www.tessrnet.com/
- http://www.imaainstitution.org/
- http://www.blossomkitchenindia.com/
- http://www.ashartacademy.com/
- http://www.krishnawriting.com/
- http://www.devrajgroups.com/
- http://www.dileepmehendale.com/
- http://www.ibcinstitute.in/
- http://www.linewidthinteriors.com/
- http://www.nashikinfrastructure.com/
- http://www.rampawarphotography.com/
- http://www.roopdarshanphotostudio.co.in/
- http://www.sanmaniso.com/
- http://www.sungeyser.co.in/
- http://www.swfs.co.in/

- http://www.vetrixnutrition.com/
- http://www.unicoladhesive.com/
- http://www.vishalsmodak.in/
- http://www.trimbakvidhi.com/

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Domain: Web Development

Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery, AngularJS

Operating System: Windows 7/8/10 Tools Used: Dreamviewer, Photoshop

# **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION**

M.Sc (Comp Sci.) Passed with 66.28%, GRADE: A, CGPA: 4.8 from Pune University, 2015.

B.Sc (Comp Sci.) Passed with 50.00% from Pune University, 2013. HSC Passed with 55% from B.K. Kawale Vidyalay, Rajaramnagar, 2009. SSC Passed with 69% from B.K. Kawale Vidyalay, Rajaramnagar, 2007.

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 2nd Feb 1992

Gender: Male

Address: A / P Jopul, Tal : Dindori, Dist : Nashik Languages Known: English, Hindi & Marathi

# **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Abhishek Suresh Savkar.